hi brothers and sisters this is eya on
eya censored supernatural bible changes
on youtube today is the 17th of may
2022 and this video i'm going to show
you variations of the king james bible
changes that's right we are seeing
variations within the king james bible
as it is satanically changing
if you are new to my channel
i beg of you to watch this entire video
go grab your king james bible and follow
along and open up your bible and take a
look and see what yours says
for these verses
and then go take a look at the rest of
my videos
on my channel and compare it to your
king james bible
we are seeing lying signs and wonders
happen right now
every bible in every language across the
earth appears to be under satanic
assault and supernaturally changing
and on my channel
i am disclosing these changes and i have
been since 2016
on various channels and of course
they've been censored on youtube but i
want to go ahead and i want to show you
what my brother
dutch sent
from canada
he's a member of our community
and
he sent these to me and i'm also going
to share with you
images from one of my king james bibles
to show you
these variations
and let me know what your bible says in
the comments below
so i want to start with this
this was the cover of one of his king
james bible it's a sword
study bible
and he's finding inconsistencies in this
translation but we are able to find
residual that's right he has some things
that are not changed
in this particular bible
will it continue to stay this way time
will tell but let me go and show you a
few things
in his sword study bible king james
bible
he still is able to see the
capitalizations
of the pronouns of god which is such a
blessing
because in all of my king james bibles
the pronouns for god and the titles of
god
are lower case
it's absolutely crazy
now here's an example from his sword
study bible i will show you a few
changes here
is that the book of psalms is now just
called psalm and it's singular instead
of plural
but i will show you in my king james
bible that it still has psalms at the
very top what does yours say psalm
singular or psalms plural
but anyway in this verse this is psalm
verse 7 verse 78 verse 56 you can see
that most high god is still capitalized
praise the lord and you can also see
that his testimonies the word his for
god is also
capitalized praise the lord
let me know what your says
there are other changes here but i do
want to show you what my king james
bible says for psalms 78
verse 56 you can see that most high are
no longer
capitalized and neither is the word his
this is a 1958 authorized king james
bible
and it has
so many changes that even on this page
but i just also want to point out that
psalms plural is still in the upper
corner of these pages praise the lord
now the next one i want to show you is
in his concordance
and i don't know i think this is his
sword study bible and you can see
that in his concordance he has the word
demon and demons
spiritual
um
being at enmity with god
and then you have correlated scripture
passages
well the crazy thing is the word demon
and demons have been erased from the
king james bible you can no longer find
demon or demons in the king james bible
so this concordance
has residual
showing proof
that this word was always in the king
james bible but of course we as
believers knew and know
the demons were in the bible
they've been changed to devil and devils
go look go do your own research as i
always encourage my listeners to do
be a berean and by the way
you can no longer find that in the book
of acts be a berean it's been erased
as so many other words have been
erased from the bible
now i also want to remind you or show
you that the word music
music
no longer exists
in the king james bible
it's been erased
i want to know whether or not your
kingdom's bible still has the word
m-u-s-i-c
music spelled just like this the correct
way
in your bible
well our brother dutch sent me this
image from his king james bible this is
first this is first chronicles chapter
verses 16 and he said
praise the lord he found residual
this music in this passage has not been
changed it has not
it's still there
but in all the other instances it's like
my king james bible and now has a k at
the end i'll show you in just a minute
do you have music spelled correctly in
your bible for this passage in first
chronicles 15 16 let me know
there are other changes in this verse
but i just want to show you music
spelled correctly but if you look online
as you can see this king james bible
online is saying that music no longer
exists in the bible
now if i go and i show you not if i'm
going to show you
my king james bible
one of them for first chronicles 15
verse 16 and you can see
it says
music with a k
so that is definitely a change and this
verse has other new words in it and also
italicized words it's totally crazy what
we're seeing in our bibles
so now music
is misspelt
in my king james bibles and it has an
added k
how crazy is that
but is it more crazy
that our brother has
residual in his own king james bible one
time yeah
praise the lord for residual the enemy
is so messy as he's rewriting our bibles
and we're able to find mistakes
over and over again
so now let me show you this this is his
sword study bible king james bible
and it says the gospel according to mark
now i just remember matthew mark luke
and john as the titles to the gospels
what about you
now i know we would reference you know
the gospel according to mark the gospel
according to matthew and we would say
that but i didn't know that as a title
to the book of mark
in his
king james bible this sword study bible
his header says the gospel according to
mark
well in my king james bible it says this
the gospel according to saint mark
that's right the gospel according to
saint mark what does your say
has saint been added in there
let me know
it used to just be mark
now i want to show you this this is one
of his king james bible where i'm not
sure if it's king james
but it says the emphasized bible new
translation
and you can see it looks obviously
really old and it's by um
[Music]
yeah it's just an old bible
and actually i have the date right here
for you copyright
1897. do you see that
1897.
well take a look at this
this particular bible translation now
says
ecclesiastes or
the proclaimer
that's right
ecclesiastes or the proclaimer
how weird is that now there are other
changes on this page
but i want to go ahead and move forward
on this page you can see
that they have all types of new symbols
and um punctuation
and
other crazy things on this page and i
think it's in the process of being
altered
you can even see in verse 12 it says i
the proclaimer do you see that
i the proclaimer no it was just
ecclesiastes
now in my king james bible authorized
king james bible it's been changed to
from ecclesiastes to ecclesiastes or
the preacher
or the preacher
what does yours say does your
book of ecclesiastes say ecclesiastes
or does it say ecclesiastes or the
preacher or ecclesiastes
or the proclaimer
how crazy is this right yeah go look
at every single title in your king james
bible because they've all been changed
most of them
now this is a letter of paul to the
ephesians now again
i remember referencing the letter of
paul to the ephesians but i only
remember the title being ephesians
so his sword study bible says
the letter of paul to the ephesians
and there are other changes here that
i'm quickly going to note
let me know if you see this in your king
james bible
hyphens apostrophes and various words
it's absolutely crazy
now let me show you what my authorized
king james bible says it says this new
title
the epistle of paul
the apostle to the ephesians
again i only remember ephesians but now
we have all this
new language in our titles to the books
of the bible
absolutely crazy what does yours say
here's um an image from his sword study
bible it says the revelation to john
the apocalypse
again that's a new title for me i
remember the book of revelations
and you can see other changes in these
verses by the way i can already see them
you see apostrophes like the word jesus
is being divided by an apostrophe
i am alpha and omega has apostrophes and
even has omega has dashes in it it was
always i am the alpha and the omega
right they've omitted the word the
but anyway and there are also the other
punctuation issues in here and even bear
record as bear witness
in verse 2.
anyway i'm just going to go back to this
title here
my king james bible says this
that's right the revelation of saint
john the divine
so now
we have two people
considered divine in the king james
bible
one is jesus
jesus christ
and i must make that disclaimer because
we now have
a few more jesuses in the bible
i've covered that recently that's right
we have a couple more jesus in the bible
and not only that
but jesus now has a son called bar jesus
that's right bar jesus and he's a false
prophet
i covered that in a most recent video
about what the bible
is now saying about god you need to go
watch that long video it's filled with
changes
about god
but anyway now we have the revelation of
saint john the divine john was never
divine
not at all
so now this title
is absolutely blasphemous
i hope you can see that what does your
king james bible say let me know
lastly i'm going to point out that his
sword study bible
although it does have changes in it as
i've already pointed out as i'm and as i
mentioned
he does have the personal
pronouns the pronouns of god are now
still
capitalized praise the lord as they
should be
in my king james bible they are now all
lower case
and that's really interesting
also holy ghost we know
is new it used to be holy spirit
holy spirit
and you can see that you can find the
word spirit in the footnote here
praise the lord
do your words in your bible have
apostrophes and dashes and other
symbols on your pages that are foreign
yeah i think it's because they're in the
process of being changed it's really
crazy let me know what your bible says
for these passages and a big thanks to
dutch for sending me these images
if you are not yet right with jesus
christ if you've walked away from him
it's time to come home
jesus christ is the way the truth and
the life and no one comes to the father
but through him we are truly seeing
lying signs and wonders happen right now
this is according to bible prophecy
everything that he told us is coming to
pass
and judgment is coming swiftly
unless you repent you will not enter the
kingdom of heaven
ask jesus christ for the forgiveness of
your sins and confess jesus christ
as your lord and savior
once you make that proclamation of faith
once you cry out to him with earnestness
that you are in need of forgiveness
a wonderful beautiful
indescribable
experience will happen
and he will flood you with his holy
spirit and give you a new heart
and he will give you a desire for
righteousness which is something we
can't do in our flesh
he will give you that desire for
righteousness and holiness and he'll
begin to work out his perfect work in
you
you'll become a new creation in christ
so not only blessed here on earth with
his presence
but forever and ever and ever in
eternity we will spend it with him
the word of god is jesus
the bible told us that in john 1 1 and
the beginning was the word and the word
was with god and the word was god
the bible on earth is satanically
changing it's under attack but the word
of god endures forever and ever and ever
praise the lord
be strong and courageous brothers and
sisters do not fear or be dismayed for
the lord your god is with you wherever
you go until next time